This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
♫Always making that face whenever you see me♫
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
♫Always making that face whenever you see me♫
♫What does that mean?♫
[Present]
♫Whatever I say upset you, but you’ll get mad if I keep quiet♫
♫I really don’t know what to do♫
♫When deep down, I really like you♫
♫But you probably don’t care♫
♫Should I just say it out loud?♫
♫Or keep it all to myself and let it be?♫
♫What should I do?♫
♫I don’t know how to tell you how I feel♫
♫I’m still confused by the way you react when I’m around♫
♫I’m still afraid. Will it be all right if I say it?♫
♫So I have to hide it inside♫
♫I don’t know what to do with these feelings♫
♫Always keep dreaming of you, night after night♫
♫What should I do? I can’t just let it go on like this♫
♫But I’m too afraid to say it, so I’ll just keep it to myself♫
Flaming Chains of Love
[Previously]
You also hate her, don’t you?
I hate you a lot too!
Actually, I don’t hate you.
I like you.
Are you sure?
Yes.
But we’ve never had a good time together.
Let’s go to the mountain together then.
Can you call me ‘Phi’ like when we were little?
Phi Jah.
Did you mean me?
Of course.
Phi Jah, you’re the luckiest in the world!
Holy shit! I’m sorry.
I didn’t see anything–didn’t see you and Miss Phrao kissing.
What if your aunt hears about it?
Nasty bitch! You know how much I hate her!
But I love her!
Aunt Nee!
Miss Panee!
[Emergency Department]
Fai.
Dad!
It’s all right.
I didn’t mean it, Dad.
I was just trying to protect Phrao.
I know, sweetie.
Don’t you worry.
No matter what happens, I will always be here to protect you.
Okay?
It’s all right.
Doctor.
Yes?
Doctor, how is my aunt doing?
The patient is safe now.
She passed out due to high blood pressure caused by a sudden stress.
But her condition is stable now.
I suggest she should be kept here for observation tonight.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Doctor.
Don't worry.
She’ll be all right. Don’t worry, sweetie.
[Door opening]
Go get some rest.
You can come back again tomorrow.
But I’m worried about her.
The doctor already gave her sleeping pills.
She’ll probably wake up again tomorrow morning.
I’ve hired a private nurse to look after her tonight. Please don’t worry.
Trust me, girl.
Go get some rest.
How is Miss Panee doing?
She’s okay now.
You go on and talk to her.
I’ll go upstairs first.
Aunt Nee is all right now, don’t worry.
I was worried sick about her.
I’m sorry I made you feel that way.
It’s me who has to say sorry.
I’m sorry.
Phi Jah, do you want to go for a walk?
I don’t like it at all.
I’m worried about Aunt Nee.
But I also care about you.
If you ever have to choose,
please choose Aunt Nee first.
Why?
I know how much you love her.
I don’t want to be the cause that makes you two fall out.
I do love her a lot.
But I’m not going to let anyone take you away from me.
There’s no making choices.
I’m not going to choose anyone.
What if one day,
you really have to choose?
Then, I’m going to choose our happiness.
I promise I’ll never make you cry again.
Phi Jah.
Maybe you should go in alone.
I’m scared.
I’m right here.
I’m not going to let you face anything like that alone again.
[Door knocking]
Aunt Nee, I brought Phrao to visit you.
She wants to apologise.
Get her out of my face.
Aunt Nee.
I said get out!
Do you want me to die right here on this bed?
[A vase shattering]
I’d better go wait outside.
In the end,
you chose her…
not me.
It’s not like that at all. I love you the most.
Love? Then, why are you doing this to me?
Why her?
That girl is the cause of all this shit.
But I love her.
I genuinely love her.
You said you love her,
not me.
I’ve cared for you
since your mother passed away.
But you’re leaving me for someone who’s just come into your life.
I’ve already lost Kwan.
I can’t afford to lose you too.
You wish I'd rather be dead, don’t you?
No, don’t say that, Aunt Nee.
Then, you must choose.
It’s either me or her.
If you insist you’ll choose her,
then go on and prepare a funeral for me.
Phi Jah, how was it?
Is she still upset?
Just a little.
But you don’t look quite well.
Are you sure everything is okay?
I just feel bad for her.
Let’s go home.
Okay.
Nod!
I already heard what happened.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
But I’m more worried about Fai.
If this is too much for you,
why don’t you move to work in Bangkok with me?
I don’t think Miss Panee will ever accept you.
I’ll take care of you.
I really appreciate it, Nod.
But I can’t leave Fai here alone.
If I’m going to move there, it must be because we both agree to it.
About what you told me that you like me,
I’m afraid I can’t accept your feelings.
You’re my best fried, Nod.
And also the person I trust the most.
But that’s all I can give you.
It’s all right, Phrao.
No matter what happens, we’ll always be friends.
I will always be there for you like I’ve always been.
Thank you, Nod.
Where were you drifting off to?
A penny for your thoughts?
I was just thinking about work.
Let me see.
You’re such a bad liar.
Tell me honestly, Aunt Nee still doesn’t approve of us, does she?
But there’s no way I’d break up with you.
Me too.
The only person who can separate us is either you or me.
Your aunt can never break us apart.
I won’t let her.
I thought you’d play the angel card and told me to pick Aunt Nee.
I’ll do everything I can…
to prove myself to your aunt and make her finally accept me.
Just like how you’ve accepted that you love me.
But what actually worries me right now
is that if I choose you,
Aunt Nee said she’d kill herself.
Yes, Dad?
Are you serious?
Your aunt tried to commit a suiside this morning.
The nurse got there in time to save her.
So, the doctor has sent a psychiatrist to talk to your aunt.
The doctor said her condition is getting worse and it might escalate.
I guess it’s time she should get proper therapy with a psychiatrist.
I’m such a terrible niece to never notice her illness.
Listen,
you’ve been an amazing niece all this time.
It’s rather your aunt…
who has been too obsessed with you.
I just don’t get it.
Why is she so unhappy
to see me being in love?
She loves you…
and your mother so much.
They grew up having only each other.
I actually feel sorry for her.
She got married to a horrible man.
And ended up getting a divorce.
She was disappointed in love so many times
that she had tried to kill herself before.
Luckily, your mum was there to save her.
That’s why your mother
meant the world to your aunt.
When your mother married me
and had you,
your aunt always came to help take care of you.
But after your mother passed away,
she was so lost.
She thought she had no one left.
But somehow,
she still has you.
Looking so good!
You’re her anchor–
her everything in life.
But then you fall in love with Kaphrao.
And she’s afraid she might lose all the love you have for her.
That’s why, sweetie.
I also never thought
that the love she has for you could hurt other people this much.
Maybe after seeing a psychiatrist for a while,
she might get better.
Yes.
But the problem is…
the doctor told me that for now,
we should keep her away from whatever that arouses her to be like this.
And that’s Kaphrao.
Hang in there, my girl.
[Panee]: Are you going to leave me for someone who’s just come into your life?
I can’t afford to lose you too.
[Phrao]: I’ll do everything to prove myself to her and make her accept me.
Dad said Aunt Nee might need to see a psychiatrist.
I think that’s a good idea.
Whether your aunt said that because she really meant it or just to get your attention,
it’s seriously concerning.
But I’m worried about you too.
Actually,
I also have something to tell you.
What is it?
I’ll move to Hua Hin to work with Nam at her resort.
Why?
I don’t want to cause you and your aunt any more trouble.
And you can also focus on taking care of her.
If I’m still around, it would only arouse her illness and make it worse.
I really don’t want us to be like this.
It’s all right.
Right now, taking care of your aunt is your first priority.
We’ll only be apart for a while.
I love you, Phi Jah.
I love you too.
[Fai: Came to work alone today. No favourite assistant by my side.]
[Fai: I'm so lonely.]
[Kaphrao: It’s my first day today.]
[Kaphrao: Boss Nam is so kind. She has already assigned me to work this morning.]
[Kaphrao: No one bullies me. Life is so peaceful here but I’m not used to it at all.]
[Psychiatrist]: How are you feeling?
Are you still depressed or stressed out?
[Fai: I took Aunt Nee to see the psychiatrist today.]
I think it’s getting better. I hardly…
[Fai: She needs to be on medication for a while.]
overthink about everything like I used to.
Or having my mind stuck in a loop.
[Fai: Haven’t seen you for weeks now–miss you so much.]
Thank you, Miss.
Do you think they could build it?
Oh, don’t worry.
Our villagers are quite skillful.
[Fai: I’m so busy these days.]
Construction is their thing. You can rest assured.
[Fai: Gotta help Dad with work, and also take care of Aunt Nee.]
[Fai: After seeing a psychiatrist for a while, she’s getting much better now.]
[Fai: I hope she’ll be back to normal soon.]
[Kaphrao: Today, I took a stroll along the beach where we once went together.]
[Kaphrao: Miss you so much, Phi Jah.]
[Fai: Came to the island to inspect some work.]
Wherever I look, I could see only you.
[Fai: Wanna get stuck on the island with you again.]
[Fai: We haven't seen each other for months now.]
[Fai: I wish it'd be over soon.]
Here you go.
Oh, you’re done, dear?
I made this soup especially for you–it’s your favourite.
I’m full now.
Do you want desserts then?
You’ve been eating very little and working so hard lately.
I’m worried you might fall sick.
It’s all right. I’m really full.
Fai has done everything the way you want.
Kaphrao is also no longer here.
Why is it that you’re still looking so depressed?
How I feel is none of your concern.
It’s a lousy father like you who has always caused her trouble.
I know that in your eyes,
I’m such a terrible father.
But I only became a father for the first time when she was born.
But you should know
But all this time,
you've never admitted you're wrong.
And that’s what makes us different.
What do you mean?
I already said it.
When I make mistakes, I admit it
and try to work on myself.
But all this time, you’ve been wrong
and never admitted it.
You’ve never tried to reflect on your own mistake.
I’m a good aunt.
I’ve loved and cared for Fai like my own daughter.
Do you still remember
when Kwan was about to pass away?
She asked you to look after Fai and make her happy.
But do you think your love makes her happy,
or actually destroy her happiness?
[Phone ringing]
[Fai]: Hello, baby.
[Fai]: No, not tired at all. What about you?
[Fai]: I already ate.
[Fai]: You wanna see it? Sure.
[Fai]: Just a second.
[Fai]: Look at the sky.
[Fai]: Isn’t it beautiful?
Thank you.
Your next appointment is in the next two weeks.
You don’t need to come here with me every time.
I can ask Paen to do it.
I don’t mind at all.
When I was young, you were the one who took me to see the doctor.
Now, it’s my turn to take care of you.
Oh, has the doctor adjusted your medication?
She has removed two from the list.
That’s amazing, Aunt Nee.
I’m sure you won’t have to take any pills soon.
You’ll be as good as new like before, and stay with me for a long long time.
I’m just an old fussy lady who complains on everything.
Do you still want to stay with me for a long long time?
Of course, I promise I’ll take care of you as best as I can.
Then, before we go home,
can you stop by the floral shop for me?
Sure.
Time does fly.
Soon, I’ll also follow Kwan.
Aunt Nee, please don’t say that.
The doctor said you should try to think positive, remember?
I was just stating the truth, dear.
One day, we all have to die.
And those left behind must keep on living.
I’ve promised Kwan
that I’d take good care of you and make you happy.
But instead, all I do is make you sad.
You’ve raised me so well, Aunt Nee.
I’ve never felt incompetent or lacking in anything.
In front of your mother, you shouldn’t lie.
Tell me, have you been happy lately?
Dad, I’m heading out.
It’s dark, where are you going?
Bangkok, to discuss work for you.
Hey, you can just drive there tomorrow. No need to go now.
But I want to, so that I can stop by to see Phrao in Hua Hin too.
I haven’t seen her for months now–I miss her.
I don’t want Aunt Nee to know. That’s why this is the chance.
Up to you then. But make sure to text me when you get there.
Roger that, sir.
Okay, sir.
See you then.
Text me, okay?
Sure.
Tell her I miss her too.
Yep.
Drive safely, girl.
[Mocking] ‘I miss her’.
I’m putting my foot down right now. I miss you so bad.
I miss you too, but please drive carefully.
No need to hurry–I’m not going anywhere.
All right then, I’ll call you when I get there.
Bye.
[Phone ringing - Akanee]
Hello?
I’m Atchima’s father.
Are you Miss Atchima’s relatives?
Yes, I’m her father.
How is my niece? Is she okay? Is my niece okay?
She’s under doctor’s care at the moment.
There’s nothing to worry about.
Excuse me, these are the patient’s belongings.
I’m sorry!
Panee.
Fai, are you awake, dear?
Does it hurt a lot?
I’m okay now.
I’m sorry, dear. I’m so sorry.
Why are you apologising?
I’m sorry I’ve tired you out and caused you to–
No, Aunt Nee, this isn’t your fault at all.
From now on,
I’m not going to stop you anymore.
No matter whom you love, I’m not going to get in the way
as long as it makes you happy and doesn't get hurt.
I thought I had lost you there.
Get some rest, dear.
Phi Jah, I’m sorry.
How did you know I’m here?
Miss Panee told me about it.
Aunt Nee?
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Fai got into a car accident. She’s now at the hospital in Chumphon.
What? So, is she–
She’s okay now.
I just called to let you know in case my niece might want to see your face.
Hello, Miss Panee.
You called and told her, Aunt Nee?
Well, it’s a serious matter.
And she should know about it.
Now that Miss Panee is here, I’m leaving then, Fai.
Don’t go.
Fai needs to eat. Stay here and feed her.
Bring it to Fai.
Yes.
Phrao.
My arm hurts. Please help me–I’m hungry.
But your aunt–
Pleaseee.
My arm hurts. I’m starving too. Please.
Hmm, so good!
Look, can you feed yourself?
I need to get back to work.
Geez, how could you leave me when I’m still like this?
You’re so mean.
Just stay.
Yes?
I know you two are still together.
The reason you rushed out at night and got into an accident
was because you wanted to go see Kaphrao, wasn’t it?
This isn’t her fault, Aunt Nee.
That’s enough. I won’t hear of it.
Since you’re the cause, you have to be responsible.
You must stay here
and look after Fai until she gets better.
You’re not allowed to go anywhere.
Miss Panee.
Thank you for letting me take care of Fai.
Let’s just say, I’ll try my best to accept you from now on.
You already beat me anyway.
Fai chose you.
I never saw it that way, Miss Panee.
The love Fai has for you is different from what she has for me.
I can never take your place, Miss Panee.
I’m well aware that if Fai ever has to choose, she will choose you.
Do you really mean it?
Yes.
That’s why I’m so glad right now.
Because the person Fai loves the most
finally approves of us being together.
I only did it for Fai.
I want her to be happy.
And you’re the one who can make her happy.
It’s true that I can make her happy.
But not entirely.
The person who holds most of her love and happiness is you, Miss Panee.
Aunt.
From now on,
call me Aunt Panee.
Aunt Panee.
Thank you so much.
I knew it.
That eventually, your sweetness would win over her heart like how you’ve won over mine.
It’s actually because of you.
Aunt Nee loves you and wants you to be happy.
No, it’s actually because you’re adorable.
Phi Jah, what are you doing? Who said you could do that?
I did.
From now on, you no longer have to worry about Aunt Nee.
Is something still bothering you?
It’s about my dad.
He didn’t stop me when I told him about us.
And even gave us his blessing.
But back then,
I did a lot of bad things to him.
I was mad that he got himself a new lover.
I did everything to stop him.
But now, I finally understand
that you can’t help who you love.
He has all the rights to love whoever he wants.
And having a new lover doesn’t mean he has betrayed my mum,
forget about her, or doesn't love me anymore.
Phi Jah,
should we go apologise to your dad then?
So that this won’t keep weighing on your mind.
I want to apologise to you.
I’m sorry I’ve always misunderstood you.
Aunt Nee already told me everything–that you’re far from being a womanizer.
That you’ve never forgotten about mum.
Or me.
I’m really sorry.
I’ve never blamed you at all.
It was my fault.
I was so consumed by work I hardly had time to take good care of you.
I have to apologise to you too.
My girl.
Then, let’s just say we’re even, okay?
Sure.
From now on, I’ll take better care of you
and spend more time with you, okay?
Just act like before, I don’t mind at all.
Now that I already have Phrao,
I guess I wouldn’t have much time for you.
Okay.
That’s what I think.
Right, Kaphrao?
Yes.
About taking care of you,
I’ll leave that to Miss Wanna.
Yes?
I’d like to apologise to you too
for always behaving badly and being rude to you.
It doesn’t matter at all.
It’s rather I who came into your family and made you feel uncomfortable.
I promise that I’d only stay in my place.
And won’t interfere with the main house.
But Dad is getting quite old.
It won’t be good for him to keep going back and forth between this house and that house.
Better to have someone around to take care of him.
Hey,
I’m not that old, you rascal.
Wanna see my marathon medal? Wanna see it, huh?
You’re really something.
- Kaphrao.
- Yes?
Give her discipline for me.
You got it.
What a rascal indeed.
Tell you what, how about you compete with me in a marathon?
Do you dare?
Just name the date.
Okay! You said it yourself.
I’ll take Phrao with me too.
Oh, that’s quite a big deal.
Would you like to join too, Miss Wanna?
Oh, that’s even a bigger deal.
I’ll go cheer for them.
Okay!
Right here, the 101 mining lesson–
the first day you picked on me.
We haven’t seen each other for 15 years–
had to give you a little welcoming ceremony.
The day you disappeared, my world just came tumbling down.
Me too.
When I had to move to a boarding school,
I cried every single night.
But somehow it made me stronger, like how you once told me,
that I needed to stand on my own legs.
I’ve had no clue.
You know what?
Deep down, I’ve always prayed
that one day if we ever saw each other again,
you wouldn’t hate me anymore.
But when you finally showed up again,
I just didn’t know what to do.
So, I brought you here and kept irritating you.
Just like what a kid would do to someone she has a crush on
because she wants to get their attention.
And wants them to know.
Now that you’ve realised you were wrong,
You must promise me you’ll never bully me again for the rest of your life.
You mean, when I made you dance here?
Phi Jah!
You’re doing it again!
Please marry me.
What if I refuse?
Then, I’ll shove you down the hill.
Phi Jah! Stop joking around.
I’ll jump off with you too.
I’m not going to let you marry anyone else.
Will you marry me?
I’m not going to let you marry anyone else too.
Yes.
It’s almost time for the Khan Maak procession.
Whoa, your hands are so cold.
- Are you nervous?
- Yes.
Wow, they’re freezing.
Try it, Miss Blew.
So cold indeed.
I’m so nervous.
Thank you Miss Rose, Miss Lada, and Miss Blew so much
for helping me with everything.
Otherwise, I would’ve surely been too nervous to get anything done.
It’s really nothing. We’re a family now.
Thank you.
Breathe in…
Breathe out…
In…
Out…
Do you feel better?
Not at all.
I’m shaking all over.
[Phi Jah/ Loves/ Nong*(little sis)/ Phrao]
♫Where’s that love people are saying?♫
♫To always be by each other’s sides♫
♫The love that’s willing to sacrifice everything♫
♫Everything even my own life♫
♫Do they really exist? I’d rather not believe it♫
♫I don’t think I’ll ever fall for anyone♫
♫Love? I don’t find it interesting♫
♫Sorry about that♫
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
♫Stop right there, don’t make me confused♫
♫I’m not someone who can fall in love♫
♫No, stop–don’t come near me♫
♫Or else my heart would start to waver♫
Fai, this gate requires not only cash envelopes but also true love.
That’s right. You need to shout out loud that you love Phrao.
If it’s not loud enough, we wouldn’t let you through.
Yeah.
Phi Jah loves Phrao the most in the world!
Hmm, we still couldn’t hear it properly.
Nam, give them the envelopes.
Nice one there.
- Next gate then.
- Please.
What? You guys are also in this too?
Yes, Miss.
You won’t get through this gate so easily.
That’s right.
It’s my friend’s wedding, so it has to be very special.
Please let me in.
Young Master, you used to treat my friend so badly.
You worked her to the bone and said horrible things to her.
How could I let you through so easily?
Then, I swear before my dad,
Aunt Nee, and everyone right here–
that this foul-mouthed person
will spend the rest of her life caring for Phrao as best as she can.
And I will always cherish her forever.
That’s my girl.
It sounds quite promising.
Give us envelopes then.
Nam, the envelopes.
But…
I think this is not enough.
- What?
- Not enough. We want more!
Just a second.
Hey! Stop playing the damn music first, can you?
I can’t keep standing still at all.
Here, just take them all.
And if you still want more, get it from your Master–I’m so broke right now.
- Can I scan to pay?
- Of course, Master.
I’ll let you through then. Go ahead!
Music!
From this day onwards,
I’ll leave her in your care, Fai.
You must take really good care of her.
Kaphrao,
you’re like a daughter to me.
If you ever have a disagreement, try to calm down and talk it through.
I hope you won't fight like when you were little. Right?
Thank you, Dad.
I’m happy for you, girls.
I wish you happiness, dear.
You too, Kaphrao.
Before, I have treated you badly all because of my prejudice.
But now, I’m letting it go.
And I’ll be cheering and watching both of your love grow.
I love you to the moon and back, Aunt Nee.
I love you the most too.
I love you too, Aunt Nee.
And I love you like my own niece too, dear.
[Applause]
Fai,
do the same to her too.
Do I have to?
[Applause]
[Photographer]: Let’s have a family picture, everyone.
[Din]: Closer.
Move a bit closer.
Hey,
give her a kiss.
Really?
Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Cheers!
Yay!
Finally, our little sis is off the market for good.
Geez, you’re saying as if no one would want to marry me.
What? I was just concerned.
With you being so foul-mouthed and hot-headed, it wouldn't surprise me if you’d stay single for the rest of your life.
[Fai]: That’s harsh.
But I know there’s definitely someone who can take her as she is.
And that someone is my baby Phrao.
See? I told you.
Love isn’t something troublesome like you used to believe.
[Nam]: Yeah, that’s right.
And it isn’t something nonsense.
But rather something that brings us joy.
Yeah, it also makes you want to become a better person
for the one you love.
Everything you’ve always said about love is crystal clear to me now.
Din’s love is soft and gentle.
Nam’s love is honest and sincere.
And Lom’s love is warm and cosy.
What about mine?
How should I define it?
Hot and fiery?
- What?
- Well, you’re Fai so it’s hot and fiery.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Geez, you just love to tease her, don’t you?
But it suits her. Fiery!
What the heck is that?
Listen, how about we change it to…
Passionate–
but tender?
That’s it, Sis. It sounds so much better.
But fiery is nice too.
Maybe I’ll keep it for our wedding night tonight.
Let’s drink to your first fiery night.
Do you need a coach on your first night?
Would you like a bedside view?
I’m just worried.
No, thanks.
You can do it.
Stay focused. I know you’ll pull it off.
Yeah.
I can do it! I’m not afraid! I can do it!
Are you exhausted now, Phi Jah?
Not yet.
We still have to do that thing together.
I’ve been looking forward to it all this time.
There’s no way I’d miss it on my wedding night.
What are you talking about?
I mean getting intimate like what married couples do.
Phi Jah, you’re such a perv! Let me go now!
Come on, baby. It’s a natural thing to do.
We’re married now. Why can’t we do it?
No!
We can’t.
Phi Jah, stop it! Let me go!
Stop it! Let me go now!
You’re not gonna let go? You’re not gonna let go, huh?
Ouch! Why are you so mean, pretty face?
I’m going to shower.
If you’re tired, just go to sleep.
Can I go shower with you?
Want me to bite off another ear?
Aww, so scary.
I’m much scarier than you think.
You’ll find out soon enough.
I surrender.
[Snoring]
Phi Jah, are you already asleep?
Yes.
How can you answer if you’re already asleep?
I’m sleep talking.
Are you trying to torture me?
I’m trying to restrain myself here.
I’m not torturing you.
You are.
You don’t want me to get intimate with you.
You suddenly blurted it out like that so I was just…
Are you scared?
Then why did you push me away?
Well, I got shy.
Aren’t you shy too?
Why are you acting like you’ve done it before?
I am. And so nervous too.
But I want to try it.
Try what?
Doing what lovers do.
How?
Want me to show you?
I’m not stopping you.
I’m going to remove my hand.
So pretty!
Fifteen years ago, I wanted to surprise you with a doll.
But it turned out to be a memory that tore us apart.
Today, I want to build a wonderful memory together with you.
You’ve kept it all along?
I’ve kept it for you.
Thank you.
You know what? When I got stuck in there,
the only person I could think of was you.
I love you, Phrao.
I’m going to tell it to you every day…for the rest of my life.
I love you too, Phi Jah.
I’m going to say it until you get sick of hearing it.
No way.
I’m going to stay by your side and listen to it forever.
♫I don’t know how to tell you how I feel♫
♫I’m still confused by the way you react when I’m around♫
♫I’m still afraid. Will it be all right if I say it?♫
♫So I have to hide it inside♫
♫I don’t know what to do with these feelings♫
♫Always keep dreaming of you, night after night♫
♫What should I do? I can’t just let it go on like this♫
♫But I’m too afraid to say it, so I’ll just keep it to myself♫
♫so I’ll just keep it to myself♫
♫Where’s that love people are saying?♫
♫To always be by each other’s sides♫
♫The love that’s willing to sacrifice everything♫
♫Everything even my own life♫
♫Do they really exist? I’d rather not believe it♫
♫I don’t think I’ll ever fall for anyone♫
♫Love? I don’t find it interesting♫
♫Sorry about that♫
♫Stop right there, don’t make me confused♫
♫I’m not someone who can fall in love♫
♫No, stop–don’t come near me♫
♫Or else my heart would start to waver♫
♫Hey, who are you?♫
♫To find your way into my heart♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
[Flaming Chains of Love]
♫Is it you?♫
[North Star Entertainment]